{
  "entries": [
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-smoke-in-the-hostel",
      "s1": "i want to smoke",
      "s2": "where can i smoke",
      "s3": "i want a cigarette",
      "s4": "can i smoke dope",
      "s5": "can i smoke grass",
      "s6": "can i smoke cannabis",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I smoke in the hostel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Smoking is not permitted in any area of the hostel, including in rooms and on common area terraces. <br><br>\n\nThis policy is strictly enforced, and guests who are unable to follow it will be asked to leave. We understand that this policy may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-vape-in-the-hostel",
      "s1": "where can i vape",
      "s2": "i want to vape",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I vape in the hostel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "You are allowed to vape on the common room terrace or on the balcony of your own room (where available). Please do not vape inside the hostel.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-smoke-cannabis",
      "s1": "i want to smoke cannabis",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I smoke cannabis?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Cannabis is only legally sold in Italy for medical or industrial use. Smoking cannabis at the hostel is strictly prohibited, and we request that you do not bring cannabis into the hostel or smoke it in the surrounding area.  We understand that this policy may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-bring-my-own-alcohol",
      "s1": "byo",
      "s2": "can i bring my own booze",
      "s3": "does the hostel have a wine opener",
      "s4": "buy own alcohol",
      "s5": "drink own alcohol",
      "s6": "drink my own alcohol",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I bring my own alcohol?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We ask that guests do not bring alcohol purchased outside of the hostel into the hostel or consume it on the premises. <br><br>\n\nThis policy is strictly enforced, and guests who are unable to follow it will be asked to leave. We understand that this policy may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "when-does-noise-restriction-start-and-what-does-it-mean",
      "s1": "what time must noise restriction",
      "s2": "what time must stop making noise",
      "s3": "what time must reduce noise",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "When does noise restriction start and what does it mean?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The town of Positano has a noise restriction that begins at midnight, which is enforced by the local police. The hostel has a noise restriction that starts at 11:45pm, at which time we ask guests to maintain a conversational volume and turn off any music. <br><br>\n\nIf a guest is unable to follow the hostel's noise restrictions, we may ask them to leave. We understand that noise restrictions may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-we-play-music-and-if-so-until-what-time-at-night",
      "s1": "can i play music",
      "s2": "what time must shut off music",
      "s3": "what time must turn off music",
      "s4": "what time must stop playing music",
      "s5": "what time must reduce music volume",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can we play music and if so until what time at night?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Music can be played until 11:45pm. After this time, Positano's town hall has a noise restriction in place. While we understand that some guests may wish to play music quietly after this time, we cannot allow it for three reasons: \n\n1) Quiet music often leads to louder-than-conversational talking; <br>\n2) What one person considers quiet may not be perceived as such by others, particularly after consuming alcohol; and <br> \n3) Quiet music may gradually get turned up in volume over time. We enforce this policy and may ask guests to leave if they are unable to follow it. <br><br> \n\nIf a guest is unable to follow the hostel's noise restrictions, we may ask them to leave. We understand that noise restrictions may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-we-play-music-through-a-speaker-and-if-so-until-what-time-at-night",
      "s1": "can i use a music speaker",
      "s2": "what time must shut off speaker",
      "s3": "what time must turn off speaker",
      "s4": "what time must reduce speaker volume",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can we play music through a speaker and if so until what time at night?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Music can be played until 11:45pm. After this time, Positano's town hall has a noise restriction in place. While we understand that some guests may wish to play music quietly after this time, we cannot allow it for three reasons: \n\n1) Quiet music often leads to louder-than-conversational talking; <br>\n2) What one person considers quiet may not be perceived as such by others, particularly after consuming alcohol; and <br> \n3) Quiet music may gradually get turned up in volume over time. We enforce this policy and may ask guests to leave if they are unable to follow it. <br><br> \n\nIf a guest is unable to follow the hostel's noise restrictions, we may ask them to leave. We understand that noise restrictions may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-we-use-the-communal-terrace-after-midnight",
      "s1": "terrace close after midnight",
      "s2": "deck close after midnight",
      "s3": "patio close after midnight",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can we use the communal terrace after midnight?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Guests are welcome to use the communal terrace at any time, as long as they follow the hostel's rules. If you have any doubts about these rules, you can check the list of rules provided by the hostel. <br><br>\n\nIf a guest is unable to follow the hostel's noise restrictions, we may ask them to leave. We understand that noise restrictions may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "when-does-the-bar-close",
      "s1": "bar close time",
      "s2": "bar last orders",
      "s3": "what time is last orders",
      "s4": "what time does bar close",
      "s5": "when does bar close",
      "s6": "when are last orders",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "When does the bar close?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel is licensed to serve drinks 24 hours a day, but we typically call last orders at 11:30pm ahead of the town's noise restriction kicking-in at 11:45pm. This helps us to comply with the town's regulations and also accommodates the needs of guests who want to sleep after midnight. If you'd like to have a drink later at night, you can visit one of the beach bars or the nightclub on the main beach, which are not subject to the same noise restriction and remain open after that time. <br><br>\n\nIf a guest is unable to follow the hostel's noise restrictions, we may ask them to leave. We understand that noise restrictions may not suit everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-buy-drinks",
      "s1": "how much is it to buy drinks",
      "s2": "how much do drinks cost",
      "s3": "how much are bar drinks",
      "s4": "bar prices",
      "s5": "where can i buy drinks",
      "s6": "I want to buy a drink from the bar",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I buy drinks?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "There are three ways to pay for drinks at the hostel: <br><br>\n\n1. Purchase a meal plan that includes drinks. <br>\n2. Pay for drinks in cash at a 20% discount. <br>\n3. Order and pay for drinks by card."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-find-the-bar-menu",
      "s1": "where can i find the bar menu",
      "s2": "i want to read the bar menu",
      "s3": "i want to look at the bar menu",
      "s4": "i cannot find the bar menu",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I find the bar menu?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Please see the bar menu below.  If you want to share the menu, just show other guests the QR code located on the top right-hand-side of the menu.",
      "link1": "/en/bar-menu",
      "linkText1": "Bar Menu"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-rules-does-the-hostel-have",
      "s1": "what are the hostel rules",
      "s2": "i think there are too many rules",
      "s3": "why does the hostel have stupid rules",
      "s4": "why are there so many rules",
      "s5": "why do many rules",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What rules does the hostel have?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We have a set of rules in place to ensure the safety and enjoyment of all guests. These rules also ensure that we are legally compliant. Check out our list of rules for futher details. <br><br>\n\nIf a guest is unable to follow one or more of our rules, we may ask them to leave. We understand that our rules may not be acceptable to everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-happens-if-i-break-hostel-rules",
      "s1": "asked to leave",
      "s2": "someone broke the hostel rules",
      "s3": "i broke the hostel rules",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What happens if I break hostel rules?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "At our hostel, we rely on our guests to follow the rules and regulations that are in place to ensure the safety and comfort of all guests. We trust that our guests will do their part to maintain a respectful and orderly environment. However, if a guest demonstrates that they will not follow the hostel rules, we may ask them to leave in order to protect the well-being of other guests and the overall functioning of the hostel. Thank you for your understanding and cooperation.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "is-the-hostel-s-water-drinkable",
      "s1": "can i drink the water",
      "s2": "is the hostels water potable",
      "s3": "is the water okay to drink",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Is the hostel's water drinkable?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The tap water at the hostel is safe to drink.  It is safe to drink as delivered by the water company that supplies the hostel.  However, the hostel filters the water we receive, improving its quality and reducing its hardness. <br><br>  \n\nFor your convenience we also keep a water cooler stocked with drinking water at the bar area."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-hostel-fridge",
      "s1": "can i use fridge",
      "s2": "where is the communal fridge",
      "s3": "is there a fridge for guests",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the hostel fridge?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel has a fridge available for guests to use and is able to store perishable items.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-guest-kitchen",
      "s1": "can i use kitchen",
      "s2": "where is the communal kitchen",
      "s3": "is there a kitchen for guests",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the guest kitchen?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel does not have a kitchen available for guests to use. However, we can provide plates, knives and forks, salt and pepper, and a microwave for heating up food. We can also provide hot water upon request. Please let us know if you need any assistance or have any special requests.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-separate-out-rubbish-recycle",
      "s1": "does the hostel recycle",
      "s2": "do you separate out rubbish",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel separate out rubbish/recycle?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we have a system in place for properly dividing and disposing of rubbish. All rubbish is divided into one of five categories: paper, plastic, glass/bottles, organic, and miscellaneous. By separating our waste in this way, we are able to recycle as much as possible and reduce our impact on the environment. Thank you for your cooperation in helping us maintain a clean and sustainable hostel."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-put-my-rubbish",
      "s1": "what can i do with my rubbish",
      "s2": "where is a trash can",
      "s3": "where is a rubbish bin",
      "s4": "i want to throw away my rubbish",
      "s5": "i want to throw rubbish",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I put my rubbish?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "There are three options for disposing of rubbish at the hostel: <br><br>\n\n1. The communal terrace has bins. <br>\n2. Each room has a bin/trash can for your convenience. <br>\n3. If you need assistance disposing of large or heavy items, you can hand them to staff and we will take care of it for you. <br><br>\n\nThank you for helping us keep the hostel clean and tidy."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-bring-a-friend-relative-etc-to-the-hostel",
      "s1": "can i bring a friend to visit the hostel",
      "s2": "can i bring a visitor",
      "s3": "can my parents visit the hostel",
      "s4": "can someone visit me",
      "s5": "can a friend visit me",
      "s6": "can a friend visit the hostel",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I bring a friend / relative / etc to the hostel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We prioritize the safety and security of our guests. <br><br>\n\nThis means ensuring that only registered guests are on the premises and assessing their competency to be on the premises on an ongoing basis. As a result, we cannot accommodate people who are not staying at the hostel, including providing them with breakfast, drinks at the bar, or other daily hostelling services.  In support of this policy, we ask that our guests do not bring non-guest visitors to the hostel, and we enforce this policy strictly. \n\nIf a guest is unable to follow this policy, we may ask them to leave. We understand that this policy may not be acceptable to everyone, so we ask that you consider this before booking a stay with us. <br><br>\n\nThank you for your understanding and cooperation in maintaining the safety and security of our hostel.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FABloQ0AZYd8bz9tTDhsuSF1Ljhj-s7T6mch06P5cNk/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel Rules"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-order-a-taxi",
      "s1": "how can i organize a taxi",
      "s2": "how can i book a taxi",
      "s3": "how can i contact taxi",
      "s4": "how can i find a taxi",
      "s5": "how can i schedule a taxi",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I order a taxi?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "To request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-order-a-taxi-2",
      "s1": "hostel organize a taxi",
      "s2": "hostel book a taxi",
      "s3": "hostel contact taxi",
      "s4": "hostel find a taxi",
      "s5": "hostel schedule taxi",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I order a taxi?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "To request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-order-a-taxi-3",
      "s1": "hostel organize a taxi",
      "s2": "Can the hostel book taxis",
      "s3": "can the hostel contact taxis",
      "s4": "can hotel find a taxi",
      "s5": "can hostel schedule a taxi",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I order a taxi?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "To request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-order-a-taxi-4",
      "s1": "i want to organize a taxi",
      "s2": "i want to book a taxi",
      "s3": "i want to contact taxi",
      "s4": "i want to find a taxi",
      "s5": "i want to schedule a taxi",
      "s6": "i want a taxi",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I order a taxi?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "To request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-nearest-laundrette",
      "s1": "where can i wash my clothes",
      "s2": "how can i wash my clothes",
      "s3": "i want to wash my clothes",
      "s4": "where can i do my laundry",
      "s5": "how can i do my laundry",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the nearest laundrette?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The nearest laundrette to our hostel is called L'Arcobaleno Di Ruggiero Giuseppina & C. Sas, and it is located 350 meters or 1150 feet from the hostel. The laundrette's opening hours may vary throughout the year, so we recommend checking their Google business listing for the most up-to-date information. One convenient option when using the laundrette is to drop off your laundry, go out for the day, and then collect it at the end of the day. The laundrette staff will wash, dry, and package your clothes for you. While you can save money by washing your clothes yourself, the machines at the laundrette tend to be busy, so it may be more convenient to have the staff take care of your laundry for you.",
      "link1": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/40.6297293,14.4808914/Viale+Pasitea,+271,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6292517,14.4811277,19z/data=!4m9!4m8!1m0!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976884650085:0xc16c5e2300284dc1!2m2!1d14.4841617!2d40.6284633!3e2",
      "linkText1": "Directions & Opening Hours: Laundrette"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-hostel-s-washing-machine",
      "s1": "where is the washing machine",
      "s2": "where can guests wash their clothes",
      "s3": "where is guest washing machine",
      "s4": "where can i wash my clothes",
      "s5": "how can i wash clothes",
      "s6": "i want to wash clothes",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the hostel's washing machine?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "As per our advertised list of facilities, the hostel does not have laundry facilities on site.  This is due to limited space for both washing and drying facilities. <br><br>\n\nThe nearest laundrette is located within 350 meters or 1150 feet of the hostel.  It is called L'Arcobaleno Di Ruggiero Giuseppina & C. Sas, and it is located 350 meters or 1150 feet from the hostel. The laundrette's opening hours may vary throughout the year, so we recommend checking their Google business listing for the most up-to-date information. One convenient option when using the laundrette is to drop off your laundry, go out for the day, and then collect it at the end of the day. The laundrette staff will wash, dry, and package your clothes for you. While you can save money by washing your clothes yourself, the machines at the laundrette tend to be busy, so it may be more convenient to have the staff take care of your laundry for you. Thank you for considering this option during your stay with us. <br><br>\n\nThank you for your understanding.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities",
      "link2": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/40.6297293,14.4808914/Viale+Pasitea,+271,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6292517,14.4811277,19z/data=!4m9!4m8!1m0!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976884650085:0xc16c5e2300284dc1!2m2!1d14.4841617!2d40.6284633!3e2",
      "linkText2": "Directions & Opening Hours: Laundrette"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-dry-my-towel",
      "s1": "where can i hang towel to dry",
      "s2": "where can guests dry their towels",
      "s3": "how can i dry my towel",
      "s4": "i want to dry my towel",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I dry my towel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you need to hang your towel to dry, there are a few options to consider depending on the amenities in your room. Here are a two things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nIf your room has a terrace, you can hang your towel to dry there. This is a convenient and effective way to dry your things. <br>\nIf your room does not have a terrace, you can hang your towel to dry in your room. Just be mindful of the space and layout of your room, and try to find a spot that is well-ventilated and out of the way. <br><br>\n\nWe hope this helps with your laundry needs. If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-dry-my-things",
      "s1": "hang my things to dry",
      "s2": "where is drying rack for my things",
      "s3": "where is tumble dryer",
      "s4": "how can i dry my things",
      "s5": "i want to dry my things",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I dry my things?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you need to hang your things to dry, there are a few options to consider depending on the amenities in your room. Here are a two things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nIf your room has a terrace, you can hang your things to dry there. This is a convenient and effective way to dry your things. <br>\nIf your room does not have a terrace, you can hang your things to dry in your room. Just be mindful of the space and layout of your room, and try to find a spot that is well-ventilated and out of the way. <br><br>\n\nWe hope this helps with your laundry needs. If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-dry-my-clothes",
      "s1": "hang clothes to dry",
      "s2": "where is clothes dryer",
      "s3": "where is tumble dryer",
      "s4": "how can i dry my clothes",
      "s5": "i want to dry my clothes",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I dry my clothes?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you need to hang your clothes to dry, there are a few options to consider depending on the amenities in your room. Here are a two things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nIf your room has a terrace, you can hang your clothes to dry there. This is a convenient and effective way to dry your things. <br>\nIf your room does not have a terrace, you can hang your clothes to dry in your room. Just be mindful of the space and layout of your room, and try to find a spot that is well-ventilated and out of the way. <br><br>\n\nWe hope this helps with your laundry needs. If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-iron",
      "s1": "clothes iron",
      "s2": "where is the clothes iron",
      "s3": "where is the iron for clothes",
      "s4": "how can i iron my clothes",
      "s5": "i want to iron my clothes",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the iron?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "As per our advertised list of facilities, the hostel does not have an iron available for guests to use. However, we do have a clothes straightener that can help to smooth out any creases in your clothes. If you need to use the clothes straightener, please come see us at the bar/reception area and we will be happy to assist you. Thank you for your understanding.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-hairdryer",
      "s1": "hairdryer",
      "s2": "how can i dry my hair",
      "s3": "i want to dry my hair",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the hairdryer?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel has hairdryers available for guests to use. If you need to borrow a hairdryer, please come see us at the bar area and we will be happy to assist you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-can-i-lock-the-lockers",
      "s1": "i want to rent a padlock",
      "s2": "where can i get a padlock",
      "s3": "how can i get a padlock",
      "s4": "i want a padlock",
      "s5": "i want to lock lockers",
      "s6": "how can i rent a padlock",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How can I lock the lockers?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel has padlocks available for guests to use for a deposit of 10 euros. If you need to borrow a padlock, please come see us at the bar area and we will be happy to assist you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-change-my-towel",
      "s1": "where can i change my towel",
      "s2": "how can i change my towel",
      "s3": "i want to change my towel",
      "s4": "where can i exchange my towel",
      "s5": "how can i exchange my towel",
      "s6": "i want to exchange my towel",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I change my towel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Towels are provided to all guests as a necessary service. The hostel has a system in place to balance this commitment with environmental considerations by charging a rental fee of two euros for towel exchanges. If you wish to swap your towel, please come see us at the bar area and we will be happy to assist you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-get-another-towel",
      "s1": "where can i get a fresh towel",
      "s2": "how can i get a fresh towel",
      "s3": "i want a fresh towel",
      "s4": "where can i get a beach towel",
      "s5": "how can i get a beach towel",
      "s6": "i want a beach towel",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I get another towel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Towels are provided to all guests as a necessary service. The hostel has a system in place to balance this commitment with environmental considerations by charging a rental fee of two euros for additional towels. If you wish to get another towel, please come see us at the bar area and we will be happy to assist you - just let us know whether you need a beach or bath towel.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-store-my-bicycle-on-site",
      "s1": "where can i put my bike",
      "s2": "how can i store my bicycle",
      "s3": "how can i store my bike",
      "s4": "i want to store my bike",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I store my bicycle on site?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The closest place to park bicycles is located on the street above Positano's town hall, which is 90 meters or 270 feet from the hostel. Please note that these spaces are provided by Positano's town hall and not the hostel, and we cannot guarantee their availability or suitability for purpose.",
      "link1": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+G.+Marconi,+358,+84017+Positano+SA/Comune+Di+Positano,+Via+G.+Marconi,+111,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6293915,14.4807703,19z/data=!4m19!4m18!1m10!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!3m4!1m2!1d14.4808653!2d40.629642!3s0x133b976686c5d6c9:0x2ae94b1bb3372aa1!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976f6aed0f21:0x9032d28e2e4f9035!2m2!1d14.4817277!2d40.6291212!3e2",
      "linkText1": "Directions: Town Hall"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-park-my-car",
      "s1": "where is the nearest car parking",
      "s2": "how can i park my car",
      "s3": "find somewhere to park my car",
      "s4": "find car parking",
      "s5": "does the hostel have car parking spaces",
      "s6": "i want to park my car",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I park my car?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "As per our advertised list of facilities, the hostel does not have a dedicated car parking space. Car parking spaces are expensive, with prices being 100,000 euros or so per space. <br><br>\n\nAs an alternative, you may be able to park your car on the street for free, although it can be difficult to find a free parking spot during the peak summer months of June, July, and August. You can try searching for free parking near the bus stop located before the hostel (if you are driving from Naples/Sorrento to Positano). You can find this location by entering 'JFJG+2X Positano, Province of Salerno, Italy' into Google Maps. When parking on the street, be sure not to park on a bend in the road, in someone's driveway, or in a space reserved for tax officials or the police, as you may receive a parking ticket or have your car towed. <br><br>\n\nCar parking in commercial lots usually costs around 10 euros per hour. If you prefer the convenience of a paid parking lot, we have included links to the three closest car parks for your reference.",
      "link1": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+G.+Marconi,+358,+84017+Positano+SA/Parcheggio+Anna,+Viale+Pasitea,+173%2FA,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6291107,14.4809978,18z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m14!4m13!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976892497ecb:0x6af10bef81190cd9!2m2!1d14.4799453!2d40.6290604!3e0",
      "linkText1": "Directions: Parcheggio Anna",
      "link2": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+G.+Marconi,+358,+84017+Positano+SA/Garage+Parking+lot+fratelli+Milano,+Viale+Pasitea,+282,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6291107,14.4810084,18z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m14!4m13!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b9766225023a3:0x2fbfe23052b9b2ff!2m2!1d14.4801205!2d40.6288187!3e0",
      "linkText2": "Directions: Milano Brothers Parking",
      "link3": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+G.+Marconi,+358,+84017+Positano+SA/Parking+Ma.cri,+Viale+Pasitea,+173,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6291107,14.4809761,18z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m14!4m13!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b9768918feb1d:0x494d7496a5a4e8d0!2m2!1d14.4799019!2d40.628946!3e0",
      "linkText3": "Directions: Pacheggio Carpineto",
      "link4": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/13O3TAesRlHbk0ZtrIrL5rFctOJvRb8rFdmDIwoL990c/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText4": "Guide: Arriving by car"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-are-the-lockers",
      "s1": "where are the lockers for my things",
      "s2": "how can i lock up my things",
      "s3": "how can i secure my things",
      "s4": "where can i securely store my things",
      "s5": "i want to use a locker",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where are the lockers?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Each guest room is equipped with lockers for the safe storage of valuables."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-change-money",
      "s1": "Can the hostel change money",
      "s2": "can the hostel change currency",
      "s3": "i want to change money",
      "s4": "i want to exchange money",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel change money?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel only exchanges US Dollars.  The exchange rate is based on the current rate quoted by Google, with an additional 5% added. The rate will be rounded up to the nearest 50 cents. <br><br>\n\nFor other currencies, you may want to consider using an exchange service or withdrawing cash from an ATM, as this may be a more cost-effective option. <br><br>\n\nIn either case you may prefer to use a Western Union.  If so the nearest is located at a company called 'Mail Boxes Etc.'",
      "link1": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+Guglielmo+Marconi,+Positano,+SA/Mail+Boxes+Etc.+-+Centro+MBE+0650,+Viale+Pasitea,+348,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6293145,14.4816708,19z/data=!4m14!4m13!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976673370cab:0x98b978e15152ff66!2m2!1d14.4821508!2d40.630006!3e2",
      "linkText1": "Directions: Nearest Western Union"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-accept-us-dollars",
      "s1": "can i use US dollars",
      "s2": "can i pay in US dollars",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel accept US dollars?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you have U.S. dollars, we will be happy to exchange them for you so that you can make payment in Euros.  The exchange rate is based on the current rate quoted by Google, with an additional 5% added. The rate will be rounded up to the nearest 50 cents.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-accept-australian-dollars",
      "s1": "can i use Australian dollars",
      "s2": "can i pay in Australian dollars",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel accept Australian dollars?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "No.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-accept-canadian-dollars",
      "s1": "can i use Canadian dollars",
      "s2": "can i pay in Canadian dollars",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel accept Canadian dollars?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "No.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "does-the-hostel-accept-payment-in-foreign-currency",
      "s1": "can i use foreign currency",
      "s2": "can i pay in foreign currency",
      "s3": "Does the hostel accept payment in cryptocurrency?",
      "s4": "can i pay in cryptocurrency",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Does the hostel accept payment in foreign currency?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel can only accept payment in Euros. <br><br>\n\nIf you have U.S. dollars, we will be happy to exchange them for you so that you can make payment in Euros.  The exchange rate is based on the current rate quoted by Google, with an additional 5% added. The rate will be rounded up to the nearest 50 cents.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "why-is-positano-so-expensive",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Why is Positano so expensive?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Real estate prices in Positano are amongst the highest in the world, with only a few places like Monaco being more expensive. As a result, the cost of living in Positano is relatively high."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "why-is-the-hostel-so-expensive",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Why is the hostel so expensive?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "During the summer months, the average price of accommodation per night in Positano is over 700 euros. We strive to provide good value for money to our guests and have received positive feedback. Due to the high demand to stay with us, we believe our hostel is a good value for the price we charge."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-much-is-positano-city-tax",
      "s1": "what is positano city tax",
      "s2": "Does Positano have a city tax?",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How much is positano city tax?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Positano's City Tax is based on the type of accommodation and is charged per person. For example, the tax for a five-star hotel is higher than that for a four-star hotel. If two guests are staying in a double room, they will each be required to pay the tax."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-is-city-tax",
      "s1": "city tax what",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What is 'city tax'?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "City Tax in Italy was introduced through the Tax Federalism Act of 2011, which allows Town Halls to set their own rates and collection methods. The tax is charged per person, per night, and must be collected by the hostel at check-in on behalf of the Town Hall.  Collected City Tax is paid by The Hostel to Positano's Town Hall once per month."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "when-do-i-pay-city-tax",
      "s1": "city tax pay",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "When do I pay city tax?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If City Tax has not been paid prior to arrival, it must be paid upon arrival."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-much-is-the-keycard-damages-etc-deposit",
      "s1": "does hostel take a keycard deposit",
      "s2": "is there a deposit for keycard/damages/etc?",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How much is the keycard/damages/etc deposit?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Upon check-in, a deposit of 10 euros per guest is required to cover the cost of bed sheets, a towel, a keycard, and any potential damages. This deposit will be refunded upon checkout, provided that all items are returned and there are no damages."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "when-must-i-give-the-hostel-the-keycard-damages-etc-deposit",
      "s1": "when do i have to pay the keycard deposit",
      "s2": "when must i pay the keycard deposit",
      "s3": "when do i want to pay the keycard deposit",
      "s4": "why must i give the hostel a keycard deposit",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "When must I give the hostel the keycard/damages/etc deposit?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "When you check in to our hostel, you'll be required to provide a security deposit. The deposit must be given in cash upon arrival. Here are a few things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nThe deposit is 10 euros. <br>\nThe deposit is held as a form of security to cover any potential damages or extra charges that may occur during your stay. <br>\nThe deposit will be returned to you in full upon check-out, provided there are no damages or outstanding charges. <br><br>\n\nWe hope this helps clarify the process for providing a security deposit."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "why-does-the-deposit-have-to-be-paid-in-cash",
      "s1": "do i have to pay the keycard deposit in cash",
      "s2": "do i want to pay the keycard deposit in cash",
      "s3": "why must i pay the keycard deposit in cash",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Why does the deposit have to be paid in cash?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The deposit is a security measure, not a payment. It will be returned to you in cash upon checkout, provided that you return the keycard and there are no damages. <br><br>\n\nTo avoid the added hassle and cost of administering credit card deposits, we ask for a cash deposit upon check-in.  This allows us to maintain our room rates without charging an additional administration fee."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-request-a-bottom-top-bunk-bed",
      "s1": "i want a bottom / top bunk bed",
      "s2": "can i select a bottom / top bunk bed before i arrive",
      "s3": "can i get a bottom / top bunk bed before i arrive",
      "s4": "can i request a bottom / top bunk bed before i arrive",
      "s5": "can i select a specific bunk bed",
      "s6": "can i choose my bunk bed",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I request a bottom / top bunk bed?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "At our hostel, beds are allocated on a first-come, first-served basis. This means that we cannot guarantee specific bed assignments, including whether you'll be given a top or bottom bunk. Here are a few things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nWhen you check in, you'll be assigned a bed based on availability. <br>\nIf another bed becomes available during your stay, you can move into that bed instead - just be sure to move your belongings to the new bed. <br>\nTo ensure that we have an accurate count of available beds, we perform regular bed checks. Please be sure to keep your belongings on your assigned bed to avoid disrupting the bed check process. <br><br>\n\nWe hope this helps clarify our bed assignment policy. If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-visit-positano-if-i-have-mobility-problems",
      "s1": "mobility issues",
      "s2": "mobility is a problem for me",
      "s3": "i cannot climb stairs",
      "s4": "i cannot climb ladder",
      "s5": "i cannot climb onto top bunk bed",
      "s6": "i am disabled",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I visit Positano if I have mobility problems?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We regret to inform you that Positano may not be a suitable destination for those who have difficulty with mobility. The presence of stairs, limited space in shops, restaurants, and cafes, a lack of facilities, and limited transportation options make it challenging for those with mobility issues to fully enjoy Positano."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-must-i-do-for-checkout",
      "s1": "how can i checkout",
      "s2": "tell me how to checkout",
      "s3": "how can i checkout",
      "s4": "i want to checkout",
      "s5": "tell me how to checkout",
      "s6": "tell me about the checkout process",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What must I do for checkout?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Please bring us the bed sheets, towel, and keycard. Place the bed sheets and towel in the basket near the bar area. Hand us the keycard for the room. At this point checkout is complete."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-is-the-first-time-i-can-checkout",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What is the first time I can checkout?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Checkout commences at 7:30am. If you need to checkout before this time, please come and see us the night before. We will take you through the early checkout process and refund your keycard deposit. If you do not come to see us the night before, we will not be able to refund your keycard deposit."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-is-the-last-time-i-can-checkout",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What is the last time I can checkout?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Checkout time is 10:30am. Please respect the needs of our cleaners and ensure that you checkout on time. After this time, they need to begin their work.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-arrange-a-late-checkout",
      "s1": "request late checkout",
      "s2": "order late checkout",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I arrange a late checkout?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We do not offer a late checkout service. Our cleaners need time to thoroughly clean every room every day. However, you can store your bags with us until 4:30pm on the day of checkout. To do so, please bring your bags to us when you checkout so that we can store them for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-store-my-luggage-after-checkout",
      "s1": "store luggage after checkout",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I store my luggage after checkout?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we will store your bags for you until 4:30pm on the day of checkout. Please bring them to us around checkout time if you would like to use this service.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-must-i-do-for-check-in",
      "s1": "how can i check in",
      "s2": "tell me how to check in",
      "s3": "how can i check in",
      "s4": "i want to check in",
      "s5": "tell me how to check in",
      "s6": "tell me about the check in process",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What must I do for check in?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We require photo identification (such as a passport, national identity card, services card, or driver's license), which we will use to take down some details. Room payment, city tax, and a security deposit of 10 euros (which must be paid in cash) must also be completed. <br><br>\n\nAfter this we will provide you with WiFi details, and our welcome video, and ask that you watch the video. <br><br>\n\nOnce these steps are completed, we will assist you to your room."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-is-the-first-time-i-can-check-in",
      "s1": "check in time",
      "s2": "first time check in",
      "s3": "when check in",
      "s4": "check-in",
      "s5": "check-in time",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What is the first time I can check in?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Check-in time is 3pm.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-is-the-last-time-i-can-check-in",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What is the last time I can check in?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Reception is open until 10:30pm. If you will be arriving after this time, we will need to coordinate with you to complete an out-of-hours check-in. This requires that we are able to take payment for the room in full (ie. if payment has not already been taken in full), and provide you with instructions on how to check in when reception is closed. Please contact us as soon as you know that you will not be able to arrive during regular check-in hours so that we can make the necessary arrangements for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-arrange-early-check-in",
      "s1": "request early check in",
      "s2": "order early check in",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I arrange early check in?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "We will check guests in once the cleaners have finished cleaning the room. While we guarantee that the room will be ready for check-in at 3pm, we cannot guarantee that check-in will be possible before this time. We can store bags and offer use of our facilities from 10:30am.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-store-my-luggage-before-check-in",
      "s1": "store luggage before check in",
      "s2": "store bags before check in",
      "s3": "store luggage before check-in",
      "s4": "store bags before check-in",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I store my luggage before check in?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we can store bags from 10:30am on check-in day.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-borrow-cutlery",
      "s1": "knife fork cutlery spoon",
      "s2": "where can i get cutlery",
      "s3": "where can i get fork",
      "s4": "where can i get knife",
      "s5": "where can i get spoon",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I borrow cutlery?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we ask that you do not take the cutlery to your room. Please return it to us at the bar/reception area and we will wash it for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-use-a-microwave",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I use a microwave?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Please bring us any items that you would like to be microwaved and we will heat them for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-borrow-a-plate",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I borrow a plate?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we ask that you do not take the plate to your room. Please return it to us at the bar/reception area and we will wash it for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-borrow-a-bowl",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I borrow a bowl?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, we ask that you do not take the bowl to your room. Please return it to us at the bar/reception area and we will wash it for you.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List of hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "can-i-use-a-napkin-paper-towel",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Can I use a napkin / paper towel?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Yes, you can request them at the bar/reception area.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "List: Hostel facilities"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "how-often-is-the-hostel-cleaned",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "How often is the hostel cleaned?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Cleanliness is a top priority. We have a team of full-time, professionally trained cleaners who work hard to ensure all rooms and common areas are thoroughly cleaned every day. <br><br>\n\nIf you have a private room and would prefer to opt out of daily cleaning, please let us know. We are happy to accommodate your preferences and ensure your stay is as comfortable as possible."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "should-we-rent-a-car",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Should we rent a car?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Driving in Southern Italy can be a unique experience compared to other places you may be used to. Here are a few things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nThe roads may be narrower than what you're used to, so be extra cautious and patient. <br>\nThe driving style in Southern Italy may seem chaotic to some visitors. Try to stay calm and take extra care when driving. <br>\nFinding parking along the coast can be challenging and costly. It may be worth considering alternative modes of transportation, such as public transportation or taxi services. <br><br>\n\nTo request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222. <br><br>\n\nPlease see our guide for more information.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/13O3TAesRlHbk0ZtrIrL5rFctOJvRb8rFdmDIwoL990c/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "Guide: Arriving by car, including parking"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "should-we-come-to-positano-by-car",
      "s1": "arrive by car",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Should we come to Positano by car?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Driving in Southern Italy can be a unique experience compared to other places you may be used to. Here are a few things to keep in mind: <br><br>\n\nThe roads may be narrower than what you're used to, so be extra cautious and patient. <br>\nThe driving style in Southern Italy may seem chaotic to some visitors. Try to stay calm and take extra care when driving. <br>\nFinding parking along the coast can be challenging and costly. It may be worth considering alternative modes of transportation, such as public transportation or taxi services. <br><br>\n\nTo request a taxi, you can use WhatsApp to contact the following number in either English or Italian: +39 379 125 6222. <br><br>\n\nPlease see our guide for more information.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/13O3TAesRlHbk0ZtrIrL5rFctOJvRb8rFdmDIwoL990c/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "Guide: Arriving by car, including parking"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-breakfast-menu",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the breakfast menu?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you have a meal plan, you will receive an email with a link to an interactive menu where you can place your order. If the meal plan was included as part of your room booking, the email will have been sent to the person who made the booking. Please ask them to forward it to you so you can access the menu. <br><br>\n\nPlease note that the pay-as-you-go breakfast menu is separate from the complimentary menu. You can find a link to this menu below.",
      "link1": "/en/breakfast-menu",
      "linkText1": "Pay-As-You-Go Breakfast Menu"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-order-breakfast",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I order breakfast?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "If you have a meal plan, you will receive an email with a link to an interactive menu where you can place your order. If the meal plan was included as part of your room booking, the email will have been sent to the person who made the booking. Please ask them to forward it to you so you can access the menu. <br><br>\n\nPlease note that the pay-as-you-go breakfast menu is separate from the complimentary menu. You can find a link to this menu below.  Place your order in the morning at the bar area.",
      "link1": "/en/breakfast-menu",
      "linkText1": "Pay-As-You-Go Breakfast Menu"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-time-is-breakfast-served",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What time is breakfast served?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "Breakfast orders can be placed from 8 am each day.  <br><br>\n\nLast breakfast orders are taken at 10:30am. <br><br>\n\nIf you have a meal plan, you will receive an email with a link to an interactive menu where you can place your order.  Be sure to use the menu to place your order the day before i.e. order Tuesday's breakfast on Monday.",
      "link1": "/en/breakfast-menu",
      "linkText1": "Pay-As-You-Go Breakfast Menu"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "what-are-meal-plans",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "What are Meal Plans?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The hostel offers meal plans, which are the cheapest way of ordering food and drink.  Please see our meal plan guide for more information.  Come see us and place your order for a meal plan at the bar area."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "i-have-an-emergency-and-the-reception-bar-area-is-closed",
      "s1": "i have a medical emergency",
      "s2": "I want help and everything is closed",
      "s3": "help me",
      "s4": "i want a medic",
      "s5": "i have an emergency situation",
      "s6": "what to do in a medical emergency",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "I have an emergency and the reception / bar area is closed.",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "In the case of an emergency, please WhatsApp us immediately at the following emergency number: +39 392 929 3384. Someone from our team will come to assist you as soon as possible. Please do not hesitate to call for help if you need it. Your safety is our top priority."
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-is-the-nearest-cashpoint-and-will-it-charge-me-a-withdrawal-fee",
      "s1": "where can i get cash",
      "s2": "where can i find a bank",
      "s3": "i want get cash",
      "s4": "where can i find the nearest cashpoint",
      "s5": "how can i find a cashpoint",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where is the nearest cashpoint, and will it charge me a withdrawal fee?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "The nearest ATM is located just 70 meters (210 feet) away and does not charge any fees for withdrawals.",
      "link1": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Et1Ux3AQRsWR4tEoDututva66CmFN0vWvW3fLTjT3GM/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText1": "Directions: ATM/Cashpoint"
    },
    {
      "type": 1,
      "slug": "where-can-i-change-money",
      "s1": "Where can I change money",
      "s2": "where can i exchange money",
      "s3": "how can i change money",
      "s4": "how can i exchange money",
      "s5": "where is the nearest place to change money",
      "s6": "where is the nearest place to exchange money",
      "humanReadableQuestion": "Where can I change money?",
      "humanReadableAnswer": "You can exchange U.S. dollars at the hostel. The exchange rate is based on the current rate quoted by Google, with an additional 5% added. The rate will be rounded up to the nearest 50 cents. <br><br>\n\nIf you prefer, the nearest Western Union is located at a company called 'Mail Boxes Etc.'.",
      "link1": "https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Brikette+Hostel,+Via+Guglielmo+Marconi,+Positano,+SA/Mail+Boxes+Etc.+-+Centro+MBE+0650,+Viale+Pasitea,+348,+84017+Positano+SA/@40.6293145,14.4816708,19z/data=!4m14!4m13!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b97669dd0003b:0xf11f22a59b1b00da!2m2!1d14.480818!2d40.629634!1m5!1m1!1s0x133b976673370cab:0x98b978e15152ff66!2m2!1d14.4821508!2d40.630006!3e2",
      "linkText1": "Directions: Mail Boxes Etc",
      "link2": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQzoMvQ34wGlnP0dgKOdt74U5LH0Lv2VbFnqG-7piKo/edit?usp=sharing",
      "linkText2": "List: Hostel facilities"
    }
  ]
}
